cashgopher.com 2013-10-05

# CashGopher - Privacy Policy

At myLot, LLC ("we" or "MyLot"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to (a) any web site ("Web site") that references this Privacy Policy and is provided by MyLot or its affiliates and (b) to those MyLot-owned software products made available to you from a Web site ("Software"). Please see below for important information on third party software products made available from the Web sites. This Privacy Policy governs information you provide to us or that we learn from you by your use of our Web sites and Software, and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances, share this information.

What We Collect and Use

**Cookies**

By accessing any Web site, MyLot may place cookies on your hard drive. MyLot uses cookies to enable you to sign in to [www.cashgopher.com](http://www.cashgopher.com/) and access your CashGopher account. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Some cookies are used only to assist you with your session on a Web site and expire automatically when you terminate that session. MyLot also uses cookies to improve the sign-in experience for [www.cashgopher.com](http://www.cashgopher.com/). For example, your CashGopher user ID may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you terminate your session. This cookie allows your user ID to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. MyLot may place a cookie on your hard disk on behalf of a sponsor when an advertisement for that sponsor is shown, so that the sponsor can measure the effectiveness of that advertisement. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer and can only be accessed or read by the domain that placed them. Though most web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually modify your browser settings to manage who can set cookies on your computer. If you choose to block our cookies, you may not be able to sign in to our website.

**User-Provided Information**

In order to utilize the services at [www.cashgopher.com](http://www.cashgopher.com/), you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information ("PII"), such as account information (user name and password), PayPal email, email address, name and company name, tax identification number, and home or work address and telephone number, as well as certain demographic information such as city, state, country and zip code. MyLot uses your PII to deliver the CashGopher services you have requested and to communicate with you, including certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from MyLot. We only collect PII that you voluntarily provide to us. If you provide a friend's email address to MyLot for CashGopher's affiliate program, we use that email address only for the purpose of sending your friend the email you requested. MyLot does not utilize PII for the purpose of displaying advertisements or for profiling and we do not sell, rent or lease PII to third parties.

**Software**

Our Software product automatically collects information from you to enable the Software's services. By installing the Software, you authorize MyLot to periodically collect certain information such as keywords and portions of Web site addresses or complete URLs from the Web sites you visit and upload this information to our servers so that we may display targeted advertisements to you while you are connected to the Internet. The Software does not collect, store, or use PII, and MyLot does not receive PII, as a result of your use of this Software.

**No Information from Minors**

You must be at least 18 years of age to use this Web site or Software.

**IP Addresses**

Your use of any Software or Web site will involve the transmission of your Internet protocol address ("IP Address") to MyLot's servers. Communication with your computer via the Internet requires this IP Address and it may be used and stored on our servers. We use IP Addresses to determine the general geographic locations of our users; we do not link IP addresses to identify you personally for marketing purposes.

**Information Disclosures**

From time to time, MyLot may contract with third party service providers to help us operate our site, conduct other aspects of our business, or improve the services that we provide to you. Some of these service providers may have access to non-PII and/or pseudonymous information collected through this Web site or your use of any Software, but only if we deem such access to be necessary to perform the services that we request. In these circumstances, we will require our service providers to commit that they will not use the information they receive from MyLot for any purposes other than to provide the required services.

Additionally, MyLot may disclose your information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with laws, regulations, or other governmental authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others. MyLot may also disclose your information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of MyLot's stock or assets in MyLot's line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization.

**Third Party Collection**

The Software may display advertisements that are hosted by third parties ("Third Party Hosted Advertisements"). These Third Party Hosted Advertisements may place cookies on your hard drive and use those cookies to tailor content delivered to you by profiling your use of a site or by advertisements you select. These Third Party Hosted Advertisements may collect information such as your IP address, your browser type and the date and time that the targeted Third Party Web site was served to you. To learn about how certain of these third parties collect and use information, visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Control of your Personal Information**

MyLot offers you choices for the collection, use, and sharing of your personal information. You may choose not to receive marketing materials from MyLot, and you may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from MyLot by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. These communications choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain MyLot services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service. You have the ability to view or edit your personal information by logging in to [www.cashgopher.com](http://www.cashgopher.com/).

**Linking to Other Sites**

A link on a Web site or on a Third Party Web site does not imply MyLot's endorsement of such linked Web site, advertiser, or product. We do not necessarily control the Web sites to which we link and, in any event, assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Any information that you provide to linked Web sites, or other third parties, is provided directly to such third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Therefore, you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any Web sites you access from a Web site or Software, and any advertisers you respond to. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by MyLot.

**Changes and Updates**

MyLot reserves the right to change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. MyLot will post those changes on the privacy page of each Web site so you can be aware of what information we collect and how we use it. Your use of a Web site or Software following the posting of any change to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any such changes. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy frequently to make sure that you understand how MyLot collects, uses, and discloses information.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about MyLot, CashGopher, any other company-owned Web site, or any Software or related services, you should consult our Web site at [www.cashgopher.com](http://www.cashgopher.com/). This site includes links to company information, answers to frequently asked questions, contact forms, and all of MyLot's s current policies for the CashGopher program.
